SACHIN SHETTY

DEVOPS ENGINEER

RESUME OBJECTIVE

Total experience of 10+ years in IT field with primary skill in implementing DevOps process on the cloud platform. Responsible for building and managing complete CI/CD flow with focus on security and continuous monitoring in place. Passionate about learning and implementing solution using advanced tools for the betterment of the process.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Mastek Ltd UK

Feb 2018 – Present: DevOps Engineer with Cloud Management

Mastek Ltd, Navi Mumbai (India)

Sep 2014 – Feb 2018: Senior Software Engineer/DevOps

Tech Mahindra, Mumbai (India)

July 2011 - Sep 2014: Technical Associate

WORKING KNOWLEDGE SNAPSHOT

- Implemented and maintained Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery pipelines in Jenkins and Azure DevOps tool for number of microservices.
- Used Bitbucket as a source code management tool, formalizing gitflow branching strategy for all the projects.
- Implemented Jenkins Shared Library structure within project to follow DRY principal.
- Integrated pipelines with NexusIQ vulnerability scans for the artefacts.
- Configured Terraform scripts/modules for various azure resources AKS, Gateways, APIM, Storage accounts etc
- Managed AKS cluster and provided support to appdev teams with their deployment issues in AKS.
- Have basic understanding of Istio and its implementation for tracing requests.
- Designed and implemented the centralized logging architecture using Elastic, Logstash and Kibana.
- Implemented ActiveMQ in High Availability mode within AKS cluster.
- Build Azure workbooks for monitoring of core services and visibility
- Configured Nagios for infrastructure monitoring

- ≤ scn.3089@gmail.com
- 07438348299
- Ilford, London
- in sachin-shetty-393b3a1b

CORE SKILLS

Azure Cloud Platform

GitHub, Bitbucket, Git

Jenkins, Azure DevOps

Azure Kubernetes Services

Terraform

Docker

Bash, PowerShell

SonarQube

NexusIQ

Nexus

Elastic, Logstash, Kibana

GitOps - FluxCD

Nagios

CERTIFICATIONS

HashiCorp Terraform Associate

MapR Hadoop Developer

EDUCATION

BE / Electronics & Telecom Mumbai University 2007-2011